They got great shipyards.
You might say that's their claim to fame
when it comes to boats they're first class.
All right then, it's settled.
We're gonna find the best shipwright in Water 7
and get him to join our crew.
Nobody told me it was gonna be this cool.
Hmm, should be okay to anchor here, right?
Holy crap, if the Mary's falling apart this easy,
we're lucky we made it here at all.
Yeah, take this.
Oh, a map, thanks for the help.
That'll be perfect.
We can head straight to the shipyard
soon as we trade in our gold.
Well, you're not gonna hear any complaints from me.
As long as the Mary gets repaired, I'll be happy.
Yeah, go Yagara!
See you later, thanks for your business
and have a safe trip.
Downtown, full speed ahead, yahoo!
Adventure in the city on the water.
Head to the Mammoth Shipbuilding Plant.
This is great!
You're the best, horsefish!
We might not be traveling in style,
but I gotta admit, this sure is handy.
I never thought riding a fish would be so comfy.
Over here, over here!
Okay, here it comes!
No problem!
Oh no, it's too high!
Get ready!
Watch out!
I got it!
Oh, yeah!
Stupid!
This is not your fault!
I was gonna get that one!
I wanna play too!
I didn't think there'd be canals running by people's houses too.
They're everywhere!
I'm trying to follow the map,
but I don't wanna miss anything.
Hey there, buddy!
Right back at ya!
Whatcha doing here?
Going sightseeing?
No, we're going to have our ship repaired at the shipyard.
I see!
In that case, you should probably go to the back street shop.
Oh, yeah!
Shopping District first!
Checkmate!
Thanks!
Ugh!
Sure!
Back Street Shopping District.
Let's take the next right!
Huh?
Oh!
Hello, mademoiselle!
Would you like to have dinner?
Uh...
Woo!
Oh!
Ah!
Don't mind him!
It's nothing!
Men around here always greet the ladies like that
when they see one passing by!
Would you stop coming?
Would you stop flirting with girls for five minutes
and get some work done for once in your life?
Yes, darling, you're the boss!
It's not that I don't appreciate a warm welcome,
but these people are so friendly, it's kind of weird!
Hey!
You with a long nose!
Huh?
Nothing!
Just saying, hey, that's all!
You're lucky I'm down here!
Huh?
Uh, we're about to go against the flow, is that okay?
We're not supposed to go up, are we?
We're not supposed to go up!
It's the wrong way!
Get off!
We're not supposed to go up!
It's the wrong way!
Go right!
Right!
Awesome!
You horsefish can swim uphill too?!
What can't you do?
Look!
The canals go to the top of the building!
Who cares?
We're going the wrong way!
Why? What's the rush?
You want to see the rest of the city, don't you?
Huh? Huh?
Look! Look! Do something! Turn around!
Oh, yeah, we're up pretty high, aren't we?
That's not what I want to hear!
He-he-he-he-he-he-he-he-he-he-he!
Whoa!
Faster!
Fast enough, thank you!
Oh...
Sorry!
Whoa!
Help me!
We're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling, we're falling!
Stop showing off!
Huh?
Best prices in town! Check us out! Take a look over here! I promise you won't regret it! We're starting our 50% off sale! Don't miss it!
Don't miss it!
We've got rare goods for the distinguished customer!
Oh man, check out all the stuff!
We ended up in the shopping district after all!
Wait, you guys took a shortcut, didn't you?
I'm sorry! You're a lot smarter than I gave you credit for!
This has got to be the biggest market I've ever seen!
Uh-huh! Whoa! Look! That bull is huge!
Whoa! Should we move? It's coming straight at us!
That thing is scary!
Pinky eats people? I wonder if this one is a king!
Huh? What's with them? They're all wearing masks! That's weird!
Wow! Neat! They're pretty!
They must be going to a party!
What the? See something?
Freshly made water-water octopus dumplings for sale!
Three water-water croquettes coming up!
I didn't know they sold food! I'm hungry! Let's buy everything!
Wait! Go back!
Hey, Lopi! Where you going?
I don't know! Ask my ride!
Huh?
Hello there! How may I help you?
I see, so you were hungry too!
Water-water meat is the Jagera's favorite food!
Although we usually cook it for humans!
Meat, huh? I'll take ten, please!
They're so good that the cooks from the gourmet town come by them in secret!
Bet you never had anything like it, huh?
So soft! Yummy!
Oh, really? They're good? Let me try one, Lopi!
No way! I'm not sharing!
Nami! He's being mean! Make him share with me!
More masks! People all over town are wearing them!
Nami!
There's something strange about this!
Nami! Are you listening?!
Hey! Some pirates are causing a ruckus at Dock 1!
What? That's not good!
Come on! We better go check this out!
Sorry, but you're not making any sense!
Need me to talk slow for you?
Sooo you repaired our ship! Sooo then I got to thinking!
And no matter how I looked at it, no matter how many times I turned our little deal around in my head, I still felt like you were charging me way too much!
You're interrupting our job!
Here's the deal! I'm not paying a single berry for the work you did!
Thanks for the repairs! They were great!
Sooo kind of you to do them for free!
Sooo you repaired our ship! Sooo then I got to thinking!
And no matter how I looked at it, no matter how many times I turned our little deal around in my head, I still felt like you were charging me way too much!
You're interrupting our job!
Here's the deal! I'm not paying a single berry for the work you did!
Thanks for the repairs! They were great! So kind of you to do them for free!
Well, cauliflower, you know what's going on?
Yes, Mr. Iceberg. Those pirates are Doc One customers. But now that the work's done, they refuse to pay. Sexual harassment.
Well, maybe it is.
Listen, sir, we take our jobs very seriously. It's not wise to mark our ship rights like that.
Captain!
Oops! Sorry!
Hey, jerk! Watch where you swing that thing! You just knocked out our...
Hey! You punks trying to pick a fight? Who do you think you are?
Oh, yeah! We haven't had a chance to test fire that cannon, have we?
No, not yet.
Damn you! You won't get away with this! We'll be back just when!
You're on ship right turn. This is what happens when you try to pull that pirate crap around here.
This is it! As soon as we take the Watergate Elevator, we'll be at the Shipbuilding Island in no time!
What's this Watergate thing?
It's that tower right ahead of us!
Attention everyone!
The elevator is ready to go!
Bulls and riders enter now! Proceed in an orderly fashion, please!
All aboard for Shipbuilding Island and Downtown Watergate!
beer at this time- 7 at this time!
Passenger llevendom!
What's this Watergate thing?
It's that tower right ahead of us.
Attention, everyone!
The elevator is ready to go.
Bulls and riders enter now.
Proceed in an orderly fashion, please.
All aboard for Shipbuilding Island and Downtown Water 7 at this time.
Passengers should enter the elevator quickly.
The gate will be closing in only one minute.
Something crazy is going to happen. I just know it.
The gate closed. It's starting.
Whoa, we're going up, we're going up, we're going up!
I see. First you go in, the gate shuts,
the water fills the elevator,
and then everybody floats to the top.
Ha ha! I still don't get it,
but it sure is awesome!
They really do use water for everything here.
Hey!
Who are you calling a moss-head jerk?
You awake?
Uh-huh.
You know where Robin went?
She's not on the ship.
Oh, I remember.
She, uh, said she was going out with Chopper.
What?
They were doing some shopping, I think.
What the hell?
Does that mean I'm stuck on this ship alone with you?
That's gotta be the most boring thing in the world!
Yep, that's why I'm sleeping.
Fine. I need to do our grocery shopping,
so I'm taking off, too.
Take good care of the boat while I'm gone.
Sleep already, huh?
Whatever.
Keep up the good work.
We've made it!
So this is the best shipyard in the whole world, huh?
It's even fancier than the rest of the town.
They've got a lot more ground to work with
than the residential district, that's for sure.
Everything's huge!
So cool!
Of course it's cool!
This place is the best!
It's great seeing the fountain up close.
It really is beautiful, isn't it?
There's a bunch of people over there.
Think something's going on at the shipyard?
Let's go check it out!
Go, Yoggana!
Look, over there!
It's Lucci!
He's so handsome!
Polly's here today, too, right?
Who cares about those guys, huh?
Now, Lulu, that's a real man.
Just look at that mustache!
Whatever!
Nobody's manlier than Tile Stone!
Hey, mister!
Hmm?
What's this crowd about?
Oh, it was just some boneheaded pirates
trying to pick a fight with the shipwrights again.
You know, happens all the time.
But our guys send them packing like always.
Those pirates will never learn their lesson.
Whoa, that's nuts!
The shipwrights can beat up pirates?
Ah, you must be tourists, huh?
The shipwrights are well.
Hmm.
They're like celebrities to us.
In fact, you might say that this crowd is their fan club.
We're always watching the Galley Lock Company.
They're strong, they're skilled,
and they're the pride of every citizen in Water 7.
Wow!
I can't wait to meet them!
Hey, Luffy!
Let's hurry up and get the gold traded in, okay?
This is fun, but it can wait till later.
Come on!
I just...
It says that we're in the Backstreet Shopping District.
Seems awfully crowded for a Backstreet, if you ask me.
Kind of neat that they have places to walk around, though.
They must have put a lot of thought into the town's design.
Yeah.
Scary!
Would you look at that?
What a beautiful woman!
She's gorgeous!
A real once-in-a-lifetime beauty!
Ugh, this place is full of Sanji's.
What is that guy selling?
It looks creepy.
It's just a mask shop.
I noticed a lot of people around town wearing them, so they must buy them from there.
It's something you wear?
I thought that was their face.
Wow, that's a big relief.
It seems the people here take the sea train to San Faldo Island, where they hold a costume carnival every day.
Huh?
How do you know that?
We just got here.
The people walking by are talking about it.
Whoa.
And do you hear everything they say?
I can't help it.
Ever since I was young, I've made it a habit to keep a critical eye and ear on my environment.
Oh.
Wow, Robin.
That's cool.
Huh.
Doctor.
Hmm?
See that?
I think we found your bookstore.
Really?
Can we go inside now?
Of course.
Be my guest.
Today is the best day ever!
CP-9.
Hey!
What are you waiting for?
If I'm in my human form, maybe it'll be okay.
Huh?
Why?
What a funny mask!
What's your costume?
Oh!
Uh...
A human...
Reindeer?
Hmm!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Well, as long as you're having fun, right?
Ha ha ha ha!
Hmm.
Oh...
Hey, wait.
Robin?
Hello?
Pity, I was hoping that we could kill you in your sleep.
You bastards sure got a lot of nerve. Who are you?
Thank you.
First on the next, One Piece, The Frankie Family and Iceberg.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!